
export const Questions=[
    {
        prompt:"RC coupling is used for?",
        optionA:"Voltage",
        optionB:"Current",
        optionC:"Power",
        answer:"optionA",
        correct:"Voltage"

    },
    {
        prompt:"The best frequency response is of?",
        optionA:"Direct",
        optionB:"RC",
        optionC:"Transformer",
        answer:"optionA",
        correct:"Direct"
    },
    {
        prompt:"Which coupling provides maximum voltage gain?",
        optionA:"Direct",
        optionB:"RC",
        optionC:"Transformer",
        answer:"optionC",
        correct:"Transformer"
    },
    {
        prompt:"Advantage of transformer coupling is?",
        optionA:"Good impedance matching",
        optionB:"Cheap in price",
        optionC:"High frequency response",
        answer:"optionA",
        correct:"Good impedance matching"
    },
    {
        prompt:"In RC coupling, the value of coupling capacitor is about?",
        optionA:"100pF",
        optionB:"10uF",
        optionC:"100uF",
        answer:"optionB",
        correct:"10uF"
    },
    {
        prompt:"Disadvantage of transformer coupling is?",
        optionA:"Expensive",
        optionB:"Poor impedance matching",
        optionC:"Poor frequency response at high frequencies",
        answer:"optionB",
        correct:"Poor impedance matching"
    },
    {
        prompt:"Select the frequency response of direct coupled amplifier",
        optionA:"Least",
        optionB:"Best",
        optionC:"Good",
        answer:"optionB",
        correct:"Best"
    },
    {
        prompt:"Which one of these is mostly used coupling technique",
        optionA:"Transformer coupling",
        optionB:"DC coupling",
        optionC:"RC coupling",
        answer:"optionC",
        correct:"RC coupling"
    },
    {
        prompt:"Calculate gain in dB for DC 2 stage amplifier if gains for individual stages are 5 and 6 ",
        optionA:"30.11",
        optionB:"28.92",
        optionC:"29.54",
        answer:"optionC",
        correct:"29.54"
    },
    {
        
        prompt:"Disadvantage of RC coupling is?",
        optionA:"Expensive",
        optionB:"Good frequenct response",
        optionC:"Poor frequency response at low frequencies",
        answer:"optionC",
        correct:"Poor frequency response at low frequencies"
    }
];